// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following are CPU scheduling algorithms?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Priority scheduling",
      "Round Robin",
      "Shortest job first" ,
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A process which is copied from main memory to secondary memory on the basis of requirement is known as ",
    answer: "No fixed length is speci",
    options: [
      "32",
      "16",
      "128",
      "No fixed length is specified"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is the proper syntax to check if a particular element is present in a list?",
    answer: "Both 1 and 2",
    options: [
      "if ele in list",
      "if not ele in list",
      "Both 1 and 2",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What will be the output of the following code snippet?  s = {1, 2, 3, 3, 2, 4, 5, 5}  print(s)",
    answer: "{1,2,3,4,5}",
    options: [
      "{1,2,3,3,2,4,5,5}",
      "{1,2,3,4,5}",
      "None",
      "{1,5}"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following functions converts date to corresponding time in Python?",
    answer: "strptime()",
    options: [
      "strptime()",
      "strftime()",
      "Both 1 and 2",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " As what datatype are the *args stored, when passed into a function?",
    answer: "Tuple",
    options: [
      "List",
      "Tuple",
      "Dictionary",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid set operation in python?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Union",
      "Intersection",
      "Difference",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " As what datatype are the *kwargs stored, when passed into a function?",
    answer: "Dictionary",
    options: [
      "List",
      "Tuple",
      "Dictionary",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How can assertions be disabled in Python?",
    answer: "Passing -O when running Python",
    options: [
      "Passing -O when running Python",
      "Assertions are disabled by default",
      "Both 1 and 2 are correct",
      "Assertions cannot be disabled in Python"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which language is Python written?",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "C++",
      "C",
      "Java",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
];

